Uptown Funk
This hit that ice cold
Michelle Pfeiffer that white gold
This one for them hood girls them good girls straight masterpieces
Stylin' Wilin'
Livin' it up in the city
Got Chucks on with
Saint Laurent gotta kiss myself
I'm so pretty
I'm too hot
Call the police and the fireman
I'm too hot,
I make a dragon wanna retire, man
I'm too hot, say my name you know who
I am
I'm too hot and my band 'bout that money
Girls hit your hallelujah
Girls hit your hallelujah 'Cos
Uptown Funk gon' give it to you 'Cos
Uptown Funk gon' give it to you
Saturday night and we in the spot
Don't believe me, just watch
Come on
Don't believe me just watch, huh
Don't believe me just watch
Hey, hey, hey, oh
Stop, wait a minute
Fill my cup put some liquor in it
Take a sip, sign the check
Julio, get the stretch
Ride to
Harlem, Hollywood
Jackson, Mississippi
If we show up we gon' show out smoother than a fresh jar of
Skippy I'm too hot
Call the police and the fireman
I'm too hot,
I make a dragon wanna retire, man
I'm too hot, say my name you know who
I am
I'm too hot and my band 'bout that money
Girls hit your hallelujah
Girls hit your hallelujah 'Cos
Uptown Funk gon' give it to you 'Cos
Uptown Funk gon' give it to you
Saturday night and we in the spot
Don't believe me, just watch
Come on
Don't believe me just watch, huh
Don't believe me just watch
Hey, hey, hey, oh
Before we leave
Imma tell y'all a lil' something
Uptown Funk you up
I said
Come on, dance
Jump on it
If you sexy then flaunt it
If you freaky then own it
Don't brag about it come show me
Come on, dance
Jump on it
If you sexy then flaunt it
Well it's
Saturday night and we in the spot
Don't believe me, just watch
Come on
Don't believe me just watch, huh
Don't believe me just watch
Hey, hey, hey, oh